

CAIO GOMES BRAGA

Mobile engineer

PROFESSIONAL RESUME

Self-taught freelance programmer for 4 years with great teamwork skills. In 2021 I started to study computer science at the Federal University of Viçosa with the objective of expanding and perfecting my skills. I have technical education in computers and some work experience. I am currently looking for a job with more stability. My professional goal is to work as a junior developer. I have the ability to develop web and mobile systems.

PRAÇA ISIDORO BINDA, 110, VILA NOVA



caiotagb@gmail.com



HTTPS://PROGRAMADOR-DE-QUINTAL.WEBNODE.COM/PO RTFOLIO/



55 + (27) 98886-0342



I HAVE MOBILITY TO CHANGE CITY / STATE / COUNTRY



LANGUAGES

- English Fluent
- Portuguese Native
- Spanish intermediary

EDUCATION

Computer Technician for the Internet Federal Institution of Espirito Santo, Colatina, Concluded, 2017-2020

Bachelor in Computer Science Universidade Federal de Viçosa, In progress. 2021

React.js and react native courses - UDEMY, Completed, 2018-2019

SKILLS

FLUTTER, NODE.JS, REACT, REACT NATIVE, PROGRESSIVE WEB APPS, NEXT.JS, SQL, REST, HTML5, CSS, PHP, JAVASCRIPT, GIT, C, C++, WORDPRESS

EXPERTISE

MOBILE DEVELOPMENT

WEBSITE DEVELOPMENT

WEBSITE MAINTENANCE

REMOTE API INTEGRATION

REPORT WRITING

UX DESIGN

EXPERIENCE

JUNIOR DEVELLOPER: APP DEVELLOPMENT AT C2

- Expanding the knwolage about the use of software architecture and clean code
- working with the project manager to deliver the product on time
- Development of communicative skills, teamwork, and design.
- Expanding the knwolage git, POO and other important technical tools
- Learning how to work with API's and backend development
- development and delivery of a flutter product to customers

INTERNSHIP: APP DEVELLOPMENT AT C2

- Learning about the use of software architecture and clean code
- Development of communication with producers and directors for job requirements. And learning working with a team
- Development of communicative skills, teamwork, and design.
- Learning git, POO and other important technical tools and knwolages

WEBSITE DEVELOPER

- During this period, websites were developed with react.js and other technologies for different customers.
- Use of social networks to contact and get customers among other sites and referrals from people who liked the service
- Skills development for website maintenance and code versioning
- Skill development for reading third-party systems documentation and Skill for independent learning.

APP DEVELOPER

- During this period, they were developed with react-native and other technologies for varied clients and personal projects.
- Use of social networks to contact and get customers among other sites and referrals from people who liked the service
- Developing skills for maintaining code sites and creating a favorable development environment
- Skill development for reading third-party systems documentation and Skill for independent learning.

INTERSHIP.

COLATINA-ES

04/2022-07/2022

INTERSHIP.

COLATINA-ES

02/2022-04/2022

FREELANCER

COLATINA-ES

06/2017-12/2021

FREELANCER

COLATINA-ES

08/2018-12/2021

EXPERIENCE

SITE DEVELOPMENT FOR DATAGEOSIS

- WORKING AND MANAGING A TEAM
- TAKING CARE OF A FULL PROJECT
- TALKING WITH CLIENTS AND MANAGING THE PRODUCT

PJ

PORTO-PORTUGAL

07/2023-PRESENT

APP DEVELOPMENT FOR US CONTRACTOR

- Talking in english with contractors in the US.
- Taking care of multiple responsabilties in varius projecs

PJ.

TAMPA, FLORIDA- US

> 07/2023-PRESENT